question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Overwatch,&quot; an allied McCree will say &quot;Step right up&quot; upon using his "
                 "ultimate ability Deadeye.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "TF2: The Heavy&#039;s voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Pistons were added to Minecraft in Beta 1.5.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Mortal Kombat was almost based on Jean-Claude Van Damme movie.", "corre ct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Starbound&quot;, the track played by the Decorated Music Box is named &quot;Atlas&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: Zombies&quot;, you can upgrade the &quot;Apothicon Servant&quot; in the "
                 "&quot;Shadows Of Evil&quot; map.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In career mode of &quot;Need for Speed: Underground 2&quot;, the first car the player can drive is "
                 "the BMW M3 GTR.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "During pre-production of &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, Mario originally was meant to shoot bullets.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
